insidify.com 2018-10-12

# Latest and verified 2018 Jobs from everywhere | Today's Job and Career advice | Career and HR Tech |

## Privacy Policy

Insidify has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. The following discloses Insidify's information gathering and dissemination practices for its website.

### Information Collected and Utilized

Insidify may collect or receive information about you when you register with the Insidify website or submit information, including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, address, gender, occupation, interests, messages sent to other users, and any other data included in a submitted profile or CV. Insidify may collect information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer, such as survey information, ratings, reviews, questions, and answers. Insidify may also record actions taken on its websites including, but not limited to, clicks, page views, IP address, and search queries. Insidify may store this information on its equipment or the equipment of third parties that it has a relationship with. Please note that emails, messages sent via your web browser, and other similar means of communication with other users are not encrypted. We strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

### Uses of Information

Insidify may use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience for you and potential employers and for all legal purposes. Insidify uses this information, including but not limited to your searches, clicks, applications, messages, postings, to provide our services and features to you, to provide your information to employers, to provide employer information to you and to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. Insidify reserves the right to charge third parties a fee for accessing your information. We may also use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities and activities that are detrimental to other users. We may use a variety of methods to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users. We may use other companies to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. Insidify may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with Insidify 's service and to administer Insidify 's site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you, your location, and your online profile and to gather broad demographic information. Nothing shall restrict Insidify from maintaining your data following your termination of your relationship with Insidify. Insidify may delete your user data at Insidify’s sole discretion.

### Contact and CV Information

Insidify 's site may ask you to give Insidify contact information (such as your name and email address) . You agree that Insidify may communicate with you, or initiate communication with you on behalf of a 3rd party, through your Insidify account or through other means made available through your contact information such as email or phone. Insidify may also use your contact information to (i) send you job alerts; (ii) create an account; and (iii) send you information about Insidify and promotional material from some of Insidify 's partners. Insidify may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor your experience on Insidify 's site, show you content that Insidify thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. To the extent you upload a CV, may make the CV and other personal information that you place on your CV available to third parties, search engines, or to the general public by posting on the internet. This may be crawled by, and displayed through, search engines when someone searches for your name. You may opt-out of this feature by editing your Privacy Settings; however, Insidify does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their caches, which may contain old public CV information. Insidify reserves the right to charge third parties a fee for accessing your information. This means that third parties can view the personal information contained in your CV and you may receive unsolicited contact from parties unaffiliated with Insidify.

### Consent

Insidify offers any user the choice to utilize the Insidify website. If you create a CV on, or apply to a job through, Insidify, you are specifically consenting to the use of any personal information you have provided to Insidify as set forth herein and in the Terms of Service.

### Links

Insidify may create links to other websites. When you click on links on Insidify, you may leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.

### Amendments

Insidify may amend this policy at any time. If Insidify is going to use personally identifiable information collected through Insidify 's site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection Insidify will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on Insidify 's website for prior to such use.

### Assignment

If there is a change of control in Insidify’s business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including personal information, could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information-handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the website, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of Insidify or the assets of Insidify you may leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.

© 2016. All Rights Reserved. www.insidify.com
